musikfriendster.com 2012-05-10

# Free Download Mp3, Video, Lirik, Lagu 4shared Gratis Index Of Mp3

**Privacy Statement**  
This privacy statement was created by index-of-mp3.com to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. Please read this statement regarding our Websites.

**Linked Web Sites**  
Our website may include links to third-party sites. Because we do not control these third-party Web sites, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by index-of-mp3.com. 

**Cookies**  
Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.   
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on www.index-of-mp3.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

www.index-of-mp3.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. index-of-mp3.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Traffic Reports**  
Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded whenever you request a page through your browser. This information cannot be used to identify specific individuals, we use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.   
Security  
With respect to security, we use industry standard encryption technologies, when transferring and receiving data from visitors on our website.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us : [musiccode@ymail.com](mailto:musiccode@ymail.com)
